老爸 儿子
Hey, Pop. -Hey, son
我仔细考虑了下 我真觉得
I've thought it over, and I really think
你应该来见见那个瑞典富豪 深入了解
you should come and see the Swede, get inside this
好吧 我...行
Oh, okay. I, uh... Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
拜托 他喜欢你
Oh, come on, he likes you
你放轻松就好  -这个嘛 你知道的 唯一的问题是
You'll keep it light. -Well, you know, the only thing is, um.
老康的婚礼  -没关系的
Con's wedding. -Oh, it'll be okay.
所以 你来吗
Are you gonna make it at all?
我们...我们给他买了!
Hmm, we... we got him some, uh.
拿破仑的啥 你之前说过的
uh, Napoleon thing, you said?
拿破仑写给约瑟芬的情书
Napoleon and Josephine letters
跟他说 我有空就打给他
Let him know that I'll call him when I have a minute
好吧  -听我说
-Right. -And, listen.
我...我现在越来越觉得
U h, I'm... I'm feeling now, more and more.
我不喜欢格丽 她处理事情的方式
I'm uncomfortable with Gerri. How she's handled things.
在司法部事件 还有一系列相关的
On the DOJ number, on the spin-off.
是吗  -是的
Oh, yeah? -Yeah.
我们想辞退她
I think we wanna let her go
好吧 这个嘛 我们再说吧
Uh, right. Right. Uh, okay, well, let's discuss
所以 你会给她打个预防针吗
So, will you give her the heads-up?
我吗  -对 我...我觉得
Me? -Yeah, I... I think
你说会更合适
it would be nicer coming from you
我的意思是 你俩 你懂的 你们..之前很亲近
I mean, you two, you know, you were... you were close.
爸  -我是说 你站我这边吗
--Uh, Dad... -I mean, you are with me?
你不是就逗我玩儿吧
You weren't just fucking me around?
当然不是 好的
Uh, well, sure, yeah. Okay, yeah
之后我们会好好收尾的
We'll make it tidy afterwards.
今天就给她个信吧 谢谢
Just give her the word today. Thank you
不用了  -就...就是确认一下
-No. -Just... Just checking, uh
他真的不想我跟你们一起去吗
he definitely doesn't want me coming with you guys?
他不想 确实
He doesn't, correct.
我应该直接跟他说吗 还是
And should I speak to him direct or..
还是跟凯莉道歉
Or to Kerry to apologize?
不用了 你在小黑账上了 低调行事吧
No, you're in the bad books. Just keep your head down.
这个嘛 我有...一系列
Well, I have a... A little list of, um,
想跟凯莉说的好话
of nice things to say to Kerry
听起来挺毛骨悚然的
Well, that sounds creepy
不可怕 就是
It's not creepy, it's.
不 听我说 格雷格 这不是你的错
No, listen. Look, Greg, it's not your fault
但他就是现在觉得你 看上去挺招人烦的
but he just finds you visually aggravating right now.
看上去挺招人烦的
" Visually aggravating "
他真小气 我不知道 你…
He's so petty. I don't know, do you...
你有争取到 瑞典所需的支持吗
Do you have all the support that you need for Sweden?
是的 我争取到了三四个人
Oh, yeah. I got, like, three, four people
为我”格“斗
Gregging for me.
格“斗 是的
" Gregging "? -Yeah.
我从猪圈绑来了 几头迷你格雷格
roped in a few little mini Gregs from the pig pen.
小格雷猪崽
Little, uh, Greg lets.
好吧 别物化我 我是个人
Okay, well, don't turn me into a word, To m. I'm a guy.
为..为什么你要有这些小人类呢
Why... Why do you have all these little guys?
用这些小格雷猪跑腿
These little Gregg ies running around?
这些小格雷格是谁
Who are these little Gregs?
船三十分钟后就要启航了 有香槟
Well, the boat leaves in 30, and there's champagne
面包托 然后抵达埃利斯岛
and canape still Ellis Island,
典礼之后 会有一些
and then after that, there'll be something more,
更丰富的美食
you know, substantial after the ceremony
瞧那艘船  -是啊
Look at that boat. -Yeah.
威拉 你就像电影里的公主
Will a, it's like you're a princess in a film.
谢谢你 我是说 总之
Thankyou. I mean, all and all,
虽然这和我们期待的不太一致
I guess it's not exactly what we expected.
但....还可以 所以
but... It's fine, so.
他会照顾你的  -他会的
He'll look after you.-He will.
我没有在看
I'm not looking.
我没有在看  -好的 我走了
-I'm not looking. -Okay, I'll go. I'm going
没有厄运
No bad luck.
您好  -康纳 这太美好了
Hi. -Oh, Connor, it's all so lovely.
是啊
Yeah.
我的天啊 看看这些年轻人
Oh, my God. Look at all the young people
我听到有些人在抱怨富人阶层了
I heard a few of them moaning about the rich
是的 这个嘛 他们倒是不介意品尝你的香槟
Yeah, well, they don't mind the taste of your champagne.
守财奴斯古治先生 恰好也是巨大财富的创造者
Mr. Scrooge just happened to be a huge wealth creator.
在狄更斯的小说中没提到这点吗
They don't mention that in Mr. Dickens's books, do they?
没有 他们没提到 真省事
No, they do not. Very convenient
向洛根斯·马克西姆斯[罗马将军]致敬 维京人的杀戮者
Hail Logan us Maximus, slayer of Vikings!
早上好 先生
Morning, sir. How are you?
所以…关于马特森 你有什么消息
So... what have you got on Mats son for me?
这个嘛 他在玩强硬手段
Well, he's playing hardball,
但 所有人都说 他还是想要交易
but everybody says he still wants the deal.
所以 我们也许需要迂回一下
So we might have to weave a little.
关于泛美网科的分拆出售 还是有些抱怨的声音 但…
There's still a bit of grumbles about the ATN carve-out, but...
这个嘛 那个不会摆在台面上  -对的
Well, that's not on the table. -Well, right.
但是 如果...你懂的 他来硬的
But, if... You know, he's playing tough.
但如果没有好处 他不会腾出时间的 所以
but if there was no upside, he wouldn't be making the time, so.
我觉得今天是时候了
I think today's the day.
我会跟希德聊聊的
I'll talk to Cyd
您是说
Oh, you mean, like..
还有格丽 罗曼办好了跟我说
And, uh, Gerri. Find out when he's done it.
好的
Okay.
卡洛丽娜  -您请说
-Karolina! -Yes?
要把格丽开了
Gerri's getting the push
好的
Oh, okay.
怎么了  -没什么
-What? -Nothing
今天我们会告知她 让法务部门也参与进来
We'll tell her today, swing in the legals
我们可以开始逐步渗入了
We can begin to let it seep.
用“邮轮事件勒索她
Hang Cruises around her neck.
就怪她没处理好 或是搞砸了 懂了
Sort of incompetence or worse. Yeah
我觉得 应该找她 走神[直译:没盯着球看]这个理由
I think the idea would be that she took her eye off the ball
清扫摊位 重新战略布局
Clean out the stalls, strategic refocus
更他妈的激进一点
A bit more fucking aggressive
你逼走希德
You push Cyd,
罗曼消灭格丽 一天就办好了
Roman knifes Gerri. All in a day's work
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 3 集
你跟马特森联系了吗 交易会正常进行 对吧
Hey What you heard about Mats son? The deal gonna be all right?
你还好吗  -是的...操你大爷
--You all right? -Hm? Yeah... Fuck you.
我挺好的 怎么了 我不知道 操你大爷
-I'm great, why? --I don't know, fuck you
我就是问问,  -操你太爷 我挺好的
-I'm just asking. -Fuck you. I'm fine
好吧  -我们好好享受
Okay! -Let's just enjoy
这场假情假意的婚礼 和浪漫的终结 会很精彩的
this sham marriage and the death of romance. It's gonna be great
好的
Okay.
如果他跟你联系了 跟我说
Let me know if you hear from him
跟我说 如果...
Let me know if..
滚吧  -你滚吧
-Fuck off. -You are.
怎么了 说话 怎么了
Yeah, what, what? Talk, talk, talk. What?
你下手了吗 你老爹想知道
Hey, you done it? Your dad wants to know.
你下手了吗
Have you done it yet?
还没有 老天爷啊 我草...我刚跟老爹
No, Jesus fucking Chri... I just got off the phone
打完电话 好吗 她...她还没到呢
With him, okay? Like, she's... she's no t here yet.
你会下手吗  -是的 我会下手的
Are you going to do it? -Yes, I'm going to do it.
我会跟你说的好吗 滚吧 你个充气小鸡鸡
I'll let you know, okay? And back off, you inflatable dicky-dick
傻逼 混蛋
Oh, fucking asshole
你好啊 格丽
Oh, hello, Gerri. How are you doing?
你看上去真美  -谢谢
-You look well. -Thank you
我看到我的一个客户了
I saw a client of mine in there.
没关系  -借过一下
Oh, no worries. -Excuse me a minute.
他不需要走的
He didn't have to go. r
怎么了 不说关于马丁的套蛋笑话了吗 或者..
What, no stupid jokes about Martyn or...
马丁 行  -关于鸡鸡的
-Martyn, okay. -... something disgusting
或者阴道的恶心笑话
about dicks or maybe vaginas?
行吧 我只是表示友好 人就不能友好了吗
Okay, I'm just being nice. Can a guy not be nice anymore?
什么
What?
什么  -你为什么不看着我
What? -Why are you not looking at me?
我...我会瞪着你的
I... I will stare at you
只要你想要 如果你如此渴望的是这个
as long as you want, if that's what you so desperately desire
怎么了 罗曼  -没什么 我就是..
What's going on, Roman? -Nothing, I'm just..
是你让我变得怪异的 你知道 并且希望这样的
You make me go weird, as you know and fully intend
但我...我们等会儿再聊 好吗
Uh, but we, um... Let's talk later, okay?
比如三十分钟后
Like, in, like, 30 or whatever
开船后 我们应该聊聊
once we set sail, we should have a chat.
什么事
What is it?
发生了什么 告诉我  -我就是需要
What's going on? Tell me. -I just need to talk
跟你聊聊 就这样 我们一会儿再说吧
with you, that's all. And we should do it later.
我们等会儿聊更好 因为
It'd be better if we did it later because, um
毫无疑问
you can no doubt tell
看看我 你就知道不是好事
just from looking at me that it's not great.
但是 你懂的 老爸这么说了 所以是一条讯息
But, you know, Dad said it. So, it's a message.
这就是我没去欧洲的原因吗
Is this why I'm not going to Europe?
你看 这不是...  -怎么回事
-Look, it's not... -What the fuck?
…正式通知 我只是提前
... official. And I'm just
提醒你一下 好吗 但确实是提前警告
heads-upping you here, okay? But, yeah, early warning
我现在不想说这个
I did not intend to talk about this right now.
但你确实…  -为什么
But, yeah, you're... -Why?
我猜 他只是不满意 你花了那么久的时间
I guess that he's just unhappy about how long it took for you
才搞定司法部  -放屁
to settle with the DOJ. -Bullshit!
我感觉 是因为罚金太多了
Well, the number and I think the fine, too big
我帮公司挺过了一场暴风雨 他妈的
I danced us through a fucking thunderstorm
而且毫发无损  -好吧 也许你只是失去了
-without us getting wet. -Okay. Guess you just lost
他的信任  -从什么时候开始的
-his confidence. -Oh, since when?
是从 你给我发你的鸡鸡照 那时候吗
Since you sent me repeated images of your genitalia?
好吧 不是  -这事发生的时候
Okay, no. -He really loved that
他可开心了呢  -别说这么消极的
when that happened. -Don't be so stupid
套话 好吗  我是在当好人 提前
and reductive, okay? I'm doing you the courtesy
告诉你 要我说如果你愿意 你大可去起诉
of letting you know. I mean, you can go legal
但是公司会用巨额
if you like, but we are gonna stuff your mouth
塞满你的嘴 这简直…
with so much fucking gold. This is...
我的意思是 我本人其实
I mean, you know that I am on, like, a human level
很明显是难过的 但是..
like, obviously sad, but.
是真的 我很抱歉 我...  -我没事
-I am. I'm sorry. Like, I... -I'm good
没事的 这算不了什么
This is fine. This is nothing at all.
谢谢你 考虑得如此周到
Thank you for the consideration.
别...
Don't...
大家好
Hi.
我们即将登船 现在开始登船流程
We'll be boarding. We'll start our boarding process,
首先 请各位宾客先上船
and we're gonna start with the red invites.
也就是亲朋好友们 欢迎登船
Family and friends. Welcome aboard
抱歉
I'm sorry.
蛋糕  -您说
-The cake. -Yes.
不够好
It's inadequate
我的意思是 我们可以把它当展示品 显然
So, I'm saying that we can have it as display, obviously.
但 我不想让宾客尝到这些 好吗
but I do not want it served, okay?
我不想看到里面的...
I don't want to see the internal..
质地 可以吗  -好的
qualities. Yes? -Okay
好的  -可以吗
-Yes. -Yes?
可以  -谢谢
Okay. -Thank you.
喂 老爸 你能
Uh, hey, Dad, can you, uh.
你能回个电话给我吗 刚才..
can you call me back? That was, uh...
我跟格丽谈得很不愉快 我
Uh, it was horrible with Gerri, so, uh, I'm just in.
我不知道...如果你不想听
I don't know if... And don't listen to this
可以不听 但是我不..
if you don't want to, but I'm not...
我不是很喜欢这样...
U h, I'm not totally okay with, uh..
难道你是在玩我吗
Are you kind of just being shitty with me?
因为你儿子马上结婚了
Cause your son is getting married
你不能指望我跪下来求你吧
and you can't fucking keep expecting me to bend over
像荡妇一样 所以我就是问一下.
for you, like, being cunty. So, I'm just asking. So, uh.
没错 我要问的是 你是小人吗
Yeah, that's the question. Are you a cunt?
好吧 记得给我回电
Okay, give me a buzz
千年杀
Kidney chop!
很好  -刺激吗
-Good. -Good?
刺激 这招不错
Good, that was a good one.
走吗  -好 走吧
Shall we go? -Yeah, let's go
我们首先去见一下
Let's, uh, may be get a head start
这些操蛋的人吧..
on all the fucky-fucky face-people, so..
嘿 很漂亮  -你们好哇
Hi. Look how lovely. -Hi.
亲亲
Oh, smooches.
船很不错  -谢谢
-Nice boat. -Thanks
早上好 恭喜  -谢谢
-Hi, congratulations. -Thank you
新郎怎么样了  -你知道的
How's the groom? --Oh, you know,
他有点担心你们
he's nervous about you guys
担心他爸 他邀请了媒体
and his dad, and he invited the press.
但他现在很纠结蛋糕的事
But he's fixated on the cake
他说“疯子蛋糕
He says it's a " Loony cake "?
是的 好吧
Yeah, okay.
那是什么
What is that?
那是...
U h, it's...
我觉得是因为..
I believe..
当他们说康纳的妈妈变得...你懂的
when they told Connor's mom was getting, you know..
进精神病院  -被带进...
Going to the funny farm. -... taken into..
精神治疗中心的时候 他们给老康吃了蛋糕
into mental health care, they gave him cake
爸还是谁来着 为了让他冷静下来
Dad and whoever, just to calm him down.
给他吃了加了很多糖的蛋糕
You know, dab of sugar, bite of cake.
所以 他连续吃了一周
So, he was eating Victoria sponge
的维多利亚海绵蛋糕
for, like, a week straight.
这样 好吧
Oh, right. Okay.
因此得名"疯子蛋糕"  -好吧
So, " Looney cake." -Yeah.
威拉 我很想跟大家打招呼
So, Will a, I'm really looking forward to saying hi to everyone
跟大家深入交流 但是 有没有地方
and mixing it up and whatnot. But is there an area where we can,
可以让我们 谈内部事情的
you know, so we don't get Roy'd to fuck
有的....
Uh, yeah. Yeah, um.
二楼有一个地方
On the second floor, there's an area.
谢谢 我真心想跟大家打成一片 聊聊他们
Thank you. I mean, I want to meet everyone and get into it all
-该死的工作…  -那什么 朱莉 请你
about their fucking jobs... -Hey, Julie, can you, um,
带他们上去  -孩子 还有一切事情 但是 你懂的
-help them get upstairs. -children and everything but, you know
谢谢  -简直难以让人相信 朱莉
thank you. -Unbelievable, Julie
你敢相信他吗  -谁是朱莉 你是吗
Can you believe this guy? -Who's Julie? You Julie?
是的  -她是朱莉
Yes. -This is Julie
你好  -这边走
-Hi. -It's right this way
好吧  -你们有消息吗
Okay. -So, uh, what are you hearing?
他会来参加吗  -妹娃 我..
-Is he coming by? -Hey. Uh, I..
我也不知道 我不知道
I have no idea, I don't know
我听说 斯德哥尔摩已经退出了 或者正在退出
U h, I'm hearing Stockholm, gone or going
没错
Yeah.
行
Okay.
马特森不愿意电话解决吗
Mats son wouldn't fix it with him on a phone r?
报业 吸收选票 掀风作浪
Journalism, taking quotes and kicking asses
你不应该跟他说话
Oh, you shouldn't talk to him.
他喜欢突然掏出大家伙 看看有没有人注意到
He likes to whip it out to see if anyone notices.
玩得太变态了 小格格…
It's a sick game, Greggy...
别继续了 坏孩子
. stop playing it. No, bad.
见到你们很高兴 大家好
Hey, nice to see you. Hey, guys
你好  -家人们
Hey. -Hey. Hey, guys
可以耽误你们一下吗  -不行
-Hey, can I grab you for a sec? -No.
不是 抱歉..
No. I... I... Sorry.
过  -我只是...我只是想恭喜你们
Pass. -I just... I just want to congratulate you
关于一切  -别碰我
on everything... -Don't touch me.
别来沾边 小格格
Get your nose out of our trough, Greggy
你觉得马特森会让爸滚蛋吗
You think Mats son is gonna tell Dad to just fuck off?
他会证明 提案就是最后的数
He'll approve the offer is what will happen
爸就得去...
Dad's gotta go fucking
吃粑粑 然后和马特森打架
lingonberry picking with Mats son.
真他妈是个PUA老混蛋
Fucking puppet mastering the old bastard
好吧 如果合作达成不了 怎么办 肯
Okay, well, what if the deal falls apart, though, Ken?
..南和内奥米那边有新消息吗
What's the... what's the latest from Nan and Naomi?
你还跟内奥米联系吗  -他会达成合作的
-Still in touch with Naomi? --He'll land it.
我们就坐等 将现金收入囊中
And we will pocket that sweet bonus loot
新郎在这呢  -来了来了
There he is. -Hey, hi, hi, hi.
所以 我想的是 爸顺道过来
Uh, hey, so, the idea is, uh, that Dad will pop by
在甲板上待一会 你们在这里
be dockside, and you guys are up here
我觉得这是最干脆的办法
And I think that's just the cleanest.
可以
Oh, okay.
你觉得他会来吗  -刚跟凯莉通完话 他觉得有希望
-You think he's gonna pop by? -Spoke with Kerry. He's hoping
那好吧  -好的
Oh, okay then. -Okay
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks. Okay
有人得告诉他实情 我们应该告诉他
Well, someone's gotta tell him. We should tell him.
我们应该跟他说
We should tell him.
别 拜托 认真的吗  -他喜欢你些
-No, come on. Really? -He likes you
好吧
Fine.
好吧  -我来当婚礼怪杰
-Fine. -I'll be the wedding Grinch
去你大爷的
Fuck you.
好运
Good luck.
天呐 让我静静...
Oh, my. Fucking leave me...
你好 操蛋小分队 在此有什么可以帮您的吗
Yeah, hello! Fucky-sucky brigade. How can I help you?
你在  -打电话 是的
Are you... -Calling, yeah.
嘿 罗曼  -在
-Hey, Roman. -Yeah
你爸现在病危
He y, uh, your dad is very sick
他病危了  -什么
-He's very, very sick. -What?
什么  -是汤姆 他说爸爸病危
What? Okay? -It's Tom. Apparently, Dad's sick
你说他病危 是什么意思 什么程度的病危
Uh, what do you mean he's sick? Like, sick, like..
发生什么了  -汤姆
-What's going on? -Tom?
汤姆 你还在吗  -他还好吗
Tom! Are you still there? -Is he okay?
发生什么了 怎么回事  -我们不知道
What's going on? What is it? -We don't know.
他还好吗  -他看起来不好
Is he okay? -He seems kind of hurt.
谁跟他在一起
Who's with him?
他的情况很严重..
He had a very serious...
严重 什么意思 我们不知道
-Serious, what? -We don't know. It's... it's..
情况非常不好 非常不好
It is very, very bad. It seems very bad
很抱歉这样通知你们
I'm so sorry to call you like this
能让他接电话吗
Can you put him on the phone?
都有谁在场 汤姆怎么回事
Who's there, Tom? What's going on?
怎么了  -是这样的.
What happened? -Uh, so,
他呼吸困难 去了洗手间
he was short of breath and he went into the bathroom,
他走开了 然后有人听到动静
and he was gone and then what it was, uh, someone heard something
他..我们很担心 然后他们就进去了
and he was... we were concerned and then they went in there
他们进去了 闯进去的吗
They... they went in, they broke in?
是闯进去的 他们有钥匙就进去了
They broke in. They, uh, they had the key and they got in there.
但是他没有任何反应 他还在里面吗
but he's nonresponsive. --Is he still in there? Did..
他...他...没有任何反应吗
He's... he's... he's nonresponsive?
对 他们…  -他有说话吗
-Yeah. They're... -Is he talking?
他..他还能说话吗  -他还有呼吸吗
--Can he... can he talk? -Is he breathing?
他们在给他做胸外按压
They're doing chest compressions.
该死 他没有心跳了吗
Oh, fuck! -Has his heart stopped?
他没有心跳了吗  -我不知道
-Has his heart stopped? -Uh, I don't know
你们...  -我不知道
-Do you guys... -I don't know.
你们的飞机上有设备吗
Do you have the machine on board?
那个心脏设备  -除颠器
-The fucking heart thing? -The defibrillator.
你们有吗  -心跳停止了才用得上
Do you have that? -Well, unless his heart has stopped
好吧 我不知道
Well, okay, I don't fucking know.
汤姆 发生什么事了 谁在负责
What's going on, Tom? Who's in charge?
小西在吗 西沃恩在吗  -谁在负责
--I... Is Shiv there? Is Siobhan there? -Who's in charge?
现在是什么情况  -不 她不在
What is going on right now? -No, she's not.
卡尔说 也许他..也许他还有呼吸
Karl said that may be he's... He's breathing, may be
你们那里有医务人员吗  -好吧 他还有呼吸
Who is medically competent there? -Okay, he is breathing?
他们受过训练 空乘们受过医疗训练
They're trained... The... the people... The attendant is trained
我把免提打开
I'm gonna put you on speaker
稍等  -那些空乘吗
hold on. -The fucking flight attendant?
机长说了… 机长一直在联系我们
The captain has spoke... The captain's been in touch
也在联系我们客舱工作人员
He is in touch and, the, uh, the cabin staff
正在接受服务团队的医疗指导
they're receiving medical, uh, advice from their service.
谁的医疗指导  -客舱服务团队的
-From who? -The cabin service.
你们有服务团队 好吧
You have a service? Okay
那是什么服务 -好吧 我们能…
what is that service? -Okay, can we be..
那个服务叫什么
What's the name of that service?
各位 能跟我们说一下详情吗 卡尔
Guys, can we be looped in on that? Karl?
他们...他们应该和他通话,  -你告诉他们去吧
-They... they should talk to him. -You tell'em, go ahead
他们应该和他通话  -是弗兰克吗
They should speak to him. -Is that Frank?
他说什么
What did he say?
弗兰克...弗兰克觉得 你们应该和你们的父亲说说话
So, Frank... Frank thinks you should speak to your dad
我可以把电话拿过去..
and I can hold the phone..
如果你们愿意 我可以把电话拿到他身边
can hold the phone near him if you like
弗兰克为什么这么觉得 汤姆
Why does Frank think that, Tom?
我想 如果..如果万一...
I guess, if... if it's a chance to,
我...我想万一 这是最后的机会了
you know. I... I think in case it's the last chance.
你他妈的什么意思 汤姆
Fuck do you mean, Tom?
他的状态不太好 罗曼 他的状态不太好
He's not in good shape, Roman. He's not in good shape.
他们在做胸外按压
They're doing chest compressions
有这个必要吗
Well, should they be doing that?
医疗指导没问题 他们是专业的
They're getting good advice. They're good people
但我觉得 你们应该跟他说说话
But I think you should talk to him
我不确定他是否还有呼吸
I... I'm not sure he's breathing.
你是认真的吗 弗兰克 该死 兄弟
You serious right now, Frank? Fuck me, man!
你们刚才还说他有呼吸
We just heard that he was breathing
弗兰克 你不应该给还有心跳的人做心肺复苏
You shouldn't do CPR to someone whose heart is going, Frank
这他妈怎么回事  -没有心跳还能呼吸吗
What the fuck is going on? -Can you breathe without a heart?
能吗  -怎么回事
Can you? -What is going on?
我带你们去找他
I'm gonna take you to him
我现在带你们去找他 把电话放在他耳朵旁
I'm taking you to him now, and I'm gonna put you by his ear.
好吧 他会听到你们说话的
Okay, he'll be able to hear you.
如果他还有听觉的话
That's... -If he can hear.
他会听到的
he'll be able to hear you.
你们最好去叫…
Uh, you might wanna get, uh.
好的 我们去叫小西 我们去叫小西
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We'll get Shiv, we'll get Shiv.
我们去叫小西  -你们最好去叫小西
We'll get Shiv. -You might wanna get Shiv.
好了 我把电话放在他耳边
Okay, I'm putting you by his ear now.
他能听到我说话吗 他还好吗
Can he hear me? Is he okay?
汤姆 他还好吗  -不 小罗他不好
Tom! Is he okay? -No, Rome, he's not okay
但你们现在可以对着他的耳朵说话
But you can speak into his ear, right now
说吧
Go ahead.
喂 爸...
Uh, hey, Dad, uh...
我希望你没事
Uh, I hope you're okay.
你没事的你...你会没事的
Uh, you're okay. You're... You're going to be okay
因为你…你是个怪兽
Uh, because you're... you're a monster.
你会赢的 因为你...
And you're gonna win.'Cause you just..
你已经赢了 你是个好…
You just win and, uh, you're a good.
你是个好人 也是个好父亲
You're a good man. You're a good dad.
你是个非常棒的父亲
You're a very, very good dad.
你做得很好
You did a good job
不行 我...对不起 我不知道该怎么说
No! I don't... I'm sorry, I don't know how to do that.
你来吧...我做不到 轮到你了
You can... I can't. Your turn.
我在他耳边吗  -是的
-Am I by his ear? -Yeah
你在他的耳边 如果他还有听觉的话
You're by his ear. If he can hear it,
他能听到的
he can hear you.
说吧  -好
Go ahead. -Okay
坚持住
Uh... hang in there.
嗯...
Yeah, um...
会没事的... -没事的
" Be okay..." -It'll be okay
你知道我们爱你 爸我们爱你
And know we love you, Dad. Okay? We love you
我爱你 爸
I love you, Dad.
真的 我爱你 知道吗
I do. I love you. Okay?
会没事的
And it's okay.
虽然你...
Uh, even though you fucking.
我不知道 我无法...我无法原谅你
I don't know. I can't... I can't forgive you
但是
But, uh...
但是 我...我
Yeah, but I... I, uh
没关系
It's okay, um.
还有就是… 我爱你
And... and... and... and I love you, uh
我不能... 我不能
I don't... I don't...
在吗 汤姆  -西沃恩在吗
-Hello, Tom? -Is Siobhan there?
肯现在就去叫她
Ken's going to get her right now.
我想他已经不在了
He's not here, I don't think
他…肯会去叫小西的
He's, uh... Ken's gonna get Shiv.
我去叫小西
I'm gonna get Shiv.
他去叫她了
He's going to get her.
你能…你能把电话放回他耳边吗
Can you... can you put me back to his ear?
谢谢你给我安排的好差事
Thanks for making me do that.
抱歉稍等...  -小西
Uh, sorry, just a sec... -Shiv.
小西 亲爱的  -是不是妈
-Shivy, honey. -Mom?
是爸 他出事了  -什么
-D ad, he's in trouble. -What?
怎么了 -他在飞机上
-What's happened? -Uh, he's on the plane
他..
And he got
我不确定...但情况很不好
Uh, I don't... It's bad and, uh,
他们在做胸外按压
they're doing chest compressions
什么
What?
你说什么肯
What? What, Ken?
来 这边走
Come on, this way
我也不清楚来龙去脉
I don't know everything, um..
他和汤姆 弗兰克 卡尔在一起
He's with Tom and Frank and Karl.
他们在和医生通话  -好吧
-and they're on the line to doctors and, uh... -Um, okay
我不知道 他当时在洗手间
I don't know, he was in the bathroom
他呼吸困难
And he had trouble breathing
我不知道...然后...
Like, I don't know... It's, uh... And.
然后 他们开始做胸外按压
And they started doing chest compressions
几分钟前 他还有呼吸  -好
-and he was still breathing a minute ago... -Okay.
但后来…情况很不好  -好
... but it's... it's very bad. -Okay, yeah
小西来了…  -好
--So, Shiv's coming, uh... -Okay
快来
He y, um...
他们... 他们觉得他已经走了  -什么
They...they think he's gone  -What?
他们觉得他走了 -怎么回事
--They think he's gone. -What happened?
什么意思  -他们觉得..
-What do you mean? -Well, they think..
他们觉得爸死了  -什么
-They think Dad died. -What?
是的  -不
-Yeah. -No.
对不起  -不
-I'm sorry. -No!
不 我不能接受
No, I can't have that!
在吗 汤姆
Hey, hey, Tom.
能让她...能让小西
Hey, can she do it? Can Shiv.
跟他说话吗  -他们一直把电话
uh, speak to him? -They've been putting us
放在爸耳边 让我们跟他说话
to Dad's ear, just to speak to him
你能把电话放在他耳边吗
Can you put her next to his ear? Okay.
我把电话给小西  -好
-I'm... I'm giving you to Shiv. -Okay
什么  -小西 我把电话放在他耳边
-What? -Hey, Shiv, I'm putting you by his ear.
好
Okay.
他还在听吗 他还能听见吗
U h, is he hearing? Is he still hearing?
我也不知道 但我把手机拿过去
Uh, I don't know. But I'm putting you there, okay?
手机在他耳边了 你可以说话了
And you're by his ear, you can go now.
你可以和他说了  -好 爸
you're talking to him now. -Okay! Hey!
喂 爸 你好
Hey, Dad. Uh, hello
你不会有事的 抱歉...
Um, you're gonna be okay. And I'm sorry..
他死了吗  -我不知道
-Is he dead? -I don't know.
我不知道 他真的死了吗
I don't know if he's dead. I s he fucking dead?
我不知道
I don't know!
汤姆
Tom?
我在
Hey, hey.
他..他还活着吗
Is he... is he even alive?
我不知道 宝贝  -那他
-I don't know, honey. -Is... is he..
你是不是在安慰我 他是不是已经走了
Are you just being nice to me? Is he gone?
他现在...我不知道...我们..
He's, uh... I don't... I don't know. We... He, uh.
我们不知道
We don't know. We don't know
我把手机放回他耳边 好吗
Okay, I'm putting you back there, okay?
好 可我…
Uh, okay. Well, um..
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
你在他耳边了
You're by his ear.
好
Okay.
我把手机放回去  -你去个安静的地方
I'm gonna put you back there. -Okay, just, like, go private.
找个安静的地方说 很怪 但你先说吧
Be somewhere private, just speak. It's weird, but speak, okay?
也许他能听到  -爸
-Like, you never know, he might hear you. -Uh, Dad?
嗨
Um, hey
爸?
Dad?
爸爸 我爱你
Daddy, uh, I love you.
求求你别走 现在不要走
Uh, don't go, please, not now.
别走 我爱你 你...
No, I, uh... I love you, you fucking.
天哪 我不..虽然没有借口.
God! I don't... Um, there's no excuses for the..
但我
But, I.
我...操
But, I... Fuck!
我不知道 我真的爱你
I don't know. I do love you
会没事的
And it's okay.
没事的 爸爸我爱你
It's okay, Daddy. It's okay, I love you
我...
I...
你想继续通话吗
Do you want to stay on?
要把手机拿开吗  -快拿走
Do you want me to take it away? -I don't want it
求你了
Please, please.
汤姆 汤姆  -喂 罗曼
Um, Tom? Tom? -Hey, Roman
现在什么情况了
What's happening? What's... What, precisely..
详细告诉我 现在什么状况
Like, tell me, precisely, what is happening right now.
好 是这样..
Okay, so, um...
我们都在这儿
Yeah, so we're all here,
我现在...
and I'm... and I'm heading to the back
往机舱后边走  -远离病人
of the plane. -Stand clear of patient.
他们现在..
And they're..
病人昏迷请远离  -他躺在前面的地上
-Shocking. Everybody clear. -He's at the front.
他们正在做胸外按压
on the floor, and they're doing chest compressions and, uh.
所以 他们还在做胸外按压吗
Okay, so they're still doing chest compressions?
对 是的 不是因为...
Yeah, yeah, they are. But not because...
我想他们必须继续做 这是标准操作
I think they have to. I think they have to keep doing that
机组的人都很好 都很负责
In the plane, people are lovely, and they're good people
我觉得他…
I think he's...
我觉得他现在 很舒服
I think they've made him very comfortable
什么 他是不是走了  -什么
What? But... but is... Is... is he gone... -What?
他走了吗...  -汤姆 他…
-He's gone... -To m, is he, uh.
他到底好不好
Is he okay, at all?
他不好 一点都不好
He's not okay. No, he's not.
他..他走了吗 汤姆
Is... is he gone, Tom?
他们说 他心跳和呼吸
I mean, they say his heart has stopped
都已经没了
and his breathing has stopped
可能有一阵子了
For a while, may be.
但在医学上 不能说明他已经死了吧
Okay, but that doesn't mean that he's dead, medically?
对吗
Right?
不知道 他们还在做
I don't know, they're... They're still doing
胸外按压  -好...那
the chest compressions. -Okay, and... and
你们什么时候降落
And when do you land?
飞机掉头了吗  你们回来了吗
Have you turned around? Are you coming back?
是的 应该没错
Yeah, I don't... I think yes. Yes.
我们正要…我们好像要回来了
We're coming to... We're heading back, I think.
好
Okay.
可以让我和驾驶舱说话吗
Can you put me through to the flight deck?
我能和驾驶通话吗 麻烦你 汤姆
Can I speak with the pilot, please, Tom?
我打给弗兰克
You know what, I'll call Frank's phone
让他帮我和飞行员通话
and he can take me to the flight deck
好吗 好
Okay. Okay
弗兰克 肯德尔会打给你
So, Frank, Kendall's going to call your phone
你拿去给飞行员 好吗
to be taken through to the pilot, okay
他打来了
Okay, that's happening
喂 肯  -杰西 我需要些东西
-Hey, Ken. -Jess, I need a few things
好  -我爸快死了
Yeah. -Uh, my dad's dying.
我现在只说事实  -明白
--I'm just going to do facts, okay? -Sure. Got it
我需要我的医生 我需要... 你还好吗
-I need my doctor and, uh, I need... -Are you okay?
他们和他的医生联系上了吗  -喂 你们
Do... Do they have his doctor? -Uh, do you have
和他的医生联系了吗
his doctor on the line?
他们…咱们和他的医生联系
Do they... Uh, do we have his doctor on..
没有 我们...正在和他们的
No, I think we got... We... we have their service.
医疗中心通话
Their medical service which they have
也和卡尔的医生联系了
and we have Karl's guy listening in
但没有联络上他的医生  -没有 没有
but we couldn't get ahold of his doctor. -No, no, no, no.
没找到他的...
They don't have his.
还有...爸的医生 该死的医生
And...and uh and Dad's doctor, Doctor fucking judith.
快给那个混蛋打电话 找他
Get that lazy fucking bastard, and get him
还有全球最好的心脏科医生
and get the best heart doctor in the world
还有最顶级的飞机医疗团队
and the best airplane medicine expert in the world
让他们待命
and get them conference d in and waiting.
把会议电话号码发给我
and send a conference call number to me
然后发给汤姆 还有卡尔 尽量帮我
and to Tom and Karl's phone, and any or all of those things
把这些办妥 一定要尽快
I will take, but I would like that in the next minute,
在两分钟内搞定 好吗 杰西  -没问题 我这就处理
-two minutes, please, Jess. Okay? -Sure. I'm on it, Ken.
好吗
Okay?
老天
Oh, boy.
肯  -我能和飞行员通话吗
-Hey, Ken. -Can I speak with the pilot?
能把手机给飞行员吗
Can you put me through to the pilot?
肯 飞行员现在不能跟你讲话
Um, the pilot can't speak to you right now, Ken.
他可以 他可以
Yes, he can. Yes, he can
他...他在开飞机 孩子
He's... he's flying the plane, son
那现在什么情况
Okay, what's, uh... What's happening?
弗兰克 我得..有什么新情况了吗
Frank, I need, uh... What's... Where's the information?
我们要...让飞机掉头
We're gonna...! We're turning the plane around
正在回泰特波罗机场
We're coming back to Teterboro
好 行
Uh-huh, okay.
好 跟他们说...告诉他们
Well, just fucking tell them... Tell them to do it, uh
不要出错 好吗
to do it right, okay?
我会的
I will, I will.
肯 我很遗憾
I'm sorry, Ken.
好
Yeah.
他走了吗
Is he gone?
弗兰克 我是说
Frank, I mean, uh..
他走了吗
Is he gone?
我不知道
I don't know.
我..他...
I...He...he...
他呼吸很急促 也很痛苦
He got very short of breath and he was hurting
而且我也…不知道
and then very...... I don't know.
肯 我也不想敷衍你
I don't want to bullshit you, Ken.
我想他已经没了 他走了
I think he went. I think he's gone.
好
Okay.
谢谢你 弗兰克 谢谢
Thank you, Frank. Thank you.
弗兰克 觉得他走了
Frank think s he's gone.
你们为什么没来找我  -我去了
Why didn't you come and get me? -I did. I did.
小西 我们去了 -不对 我刚刚…
Shiv, we did. -No, but I was.
我就在外面  -对不起
-I was right out there. -I'm so sorry. I'm sorry
你们接电话多久了
How long was it happening before?
对不起 我没...  -不对
I'm sorry, I wasn't... -No, no, no.
我们去了...但是我...  -你们没有
We did... we did but I wasn't... -No!
-因为没来得及  -我没有想到
There was, like, no time  -I wasn't thinking.
时间不够了 对不起 我没...
-There was no time. -I'm sorry. I didn't..
对不起 -没关系
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -It's okay
-对不起  -没关系
I'm sorry. -It's okay
这真的
It's just..
汤姆说 凯莉和爸说了好多话
Tom said that Kerry spoke to him, quite a bit.
对 我...不知道
Right, well, I don't... I don't know.
我不知道他听不听得到咱们
I mean,we don't know if he could hear us
好 我就是太难过了
Yeah. Just I'm sad, I guess
能知道他当时有没有用手机吗
Do we know if he was on his phone?
他有没有听过留言
He checked his messages?
小罗 没事的  -我明白
-Rome, it's okay. -Yeah, I know
就是...  -我们会没事的
-it's just... -We're okay
我不知道 我真的不知道
I don't know. I just don't know.
我说的话有没有.. -你做得很棒
-Like if I said... -You did good
我感觉...我觉得我没有
I feel... I feel like I didn't...
我有说我爱他吗
Did I say I loved him?
我觉得说了   -我很确定没有
-I think so, yeah. --I'm pretty sure I didn't.
不 我...我觉得你说了
No, I... I... I think you did
不 我没说 汤姆 能把手机
No, I don't think so. Uh, Tom, could you put me back
再拿去他耳边吗 靠 算了
to his ear? Or... Fuck it. Never mind.
就...我也不知道..
Uh, never... I don't know. I don't..
就先...别挂机
Maybe just... Let's just keep the line open.
有事我会联系你的
I'll tell you if anything happens
好  -这蛋糕...真他妈烂透了
-Okay. -That... this cake is fucked
把它扔掉  -操
Toss it over -Oh fuck
我们得去找康纳 我们得告诉他
We need to get Connor. We need to tell him.
你能去说吗 肯
Can you do it, Ken?
我...我开不了口
I think... I don't think I can.
我可以 我肯定可以 就是
I mean, I could. I definitely could, I just
谢谢
Thank you.
没事  -要我...
It's okay. -Do you want me to.
好吧
Yeah.
好的
Yeah
操  -真操蛋
Oh, fuck. -Fuck this
那是我弟弟和妹妹
That's my brother and sister.
老康  -蛋糕真是场噩梦
-Hey, Con. -Fucking cake nightmare, okay
老康 老康  -能帮我去处理下吗
Con, Con. -Would you take care of that for me?
老康 过来下  -怎么 什么事
-Con. Come here. -Yeah? What is it?
过...  -过来
-Come... -Come here.
怎么了  -这…这是私事
-What is it? -It's just... It's private.
是大事 过来下
It's serious, come here.
五分钟 好吗  -好的
-Five, okay. -Yeah.
过来 兄弟  -怎么了 什么事 这么重要
-Come here, buddy. -What is it? Is it important?
过来一会儿  -怎么了啊
-Come here for a sec. -What?
我们告诉你...
Let's get you, um...
是老爸的事吗
Is it Pop?
他还好吗
Is he okay?
怎么了 他病了吗
What is it? Is he sick?
倒是说啊  -爸在去瑞典的飞机上
What is it? -Dad's on an airplane to Sweden,
但他们现在掉头回来了
but they're coming back
我们认为他死了
We think he died.
他们…他们认为他死了
They... They think he's dead
是吗
Well, is he?
所有人都说他死了
Well, uh, everyone says he is.
我们不知道
I mean, we don't know.
他们在做胸外按压
They're doing heart compressions.
老天
Oh, man.
他真是从来没喜欢过我
He never even liked me.
老康 抱歉
Hey, Con... -Hey... Sorry
你知道吗 我很抱歉 对不起
You know what? I'm sorry. I'm sorry
我都不知道怎么就脱口而出了 他喜欢我的
I don't even know what I mean. He did. He did
我只是…从来没机会让他以我为荣
I just... I never got the chance to make him proud of me.
他死了
He's dead.
他..  -小罗在和
-He's... -Roman is on the phone
机上人员通话  -天啊
-to the plane. -Jesus.
你...你如果想跟他说话
Do you... If you wanna talk to him.
我天  -他...
Oh, man. -He's...
老康  -我不知道 我不知道
-Hi, Con. -I don't know, I don't know.
有消息吗
Anything?
我做不到 我真的不行
I can't do this, okay? I can't.
我做不到 不行 好吗
I can't. I can't do this, okay?
你好
Hi.
谢谢
Thank you.
出什么事了
What happened?
怎么回事  -抱歉 我真的很抱歉
What happened? -I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry, I'm sorry
他...
He, uh, uh..
他在飞机上…
He was on the plane and, um.
他呼吸急促…  -我...我说了
--he got short of breath, u h... -I said... I said, " Hello
傻逼玩意儿” 他当时在厕所
fucky-sucky brigade," And he was in the bathroom
他当时在厕所吗
He was... he was in the bathroom?
对 我不知道 他可能不舒服
Yeah, I don't know. He was in trouble, I guess, so
怎么…怎么回事
Wha... wha... wha... wha... What was it?
他呼吸急促  -我们啥都不确定
He got short of breath. -Well, we don't actually know
我是说 我们不知道他是不是真的死了
I mean, like, we don't know he's gone
好吧 那
Uh, okay, so,
他当时在..飞机的厕所里
he was in the... the airplane toilet.
靠 小西别说了  -然后...
-Oh, fuck. Shiv, come on. -And.
我们能把事情搞清楚吗
No, but can we please get this straight?
我们...  -要不先搞几个医生上去
Yeah, let's just... -How about we get some doctors in there?
靠谱的医生 到时候就知道怎么回事了
Some proper doctors, and then we'll know what actually happened
然后我们再聊  -当然 我是说…
-Then we can talk about it. -Sure, I mean..
他已经没了
he has gone.
我觉得他死了  -肯 我们还不确定
-I think he has died. -Well, Ken, we don't know that.
所以... -当然 我明白
-So... -Sure. I get it.
但我觉得 他们知道  -可能吧
But, like, I think they know. -Okay, okay, may be
可能就是这样  -罗曼 我觉得
-Maybe is all. -Roman, I think
你得接受
you have to accept that.
行了 我也没说什么
Okay, I'm not, like, saying anything
我只是说 我们不清楚具体情况
All I'm saying is that we actually don't know.
就是这样 我就是这意思
That's it, that's all I'm saying.
好吧 没错 但你像在说胡话
Okay, right. Well, yes, but you sound delusional
我听着...我现在是被你们针对了吗
I sound... Wha... What am I, out-fucking-voted here?
不 小罗 我只是说… 拜托 你明白的...
No, Rome, I'm just saying... Come on, you know that...
什么  -他们知道
-What?  -They know..
不 他们也不知道  -他已经
-No, no, they don't. -that he's..
不  -没事的
No! -It's okay.
他已经...  -他妈的他死了
-That he's... -He's fucking dead!
行了 但他妈也不用这么说吧
Well, okay! But there's no need to fucking say that, right?
直到确认之前 都他妈没必要
Until we know there's no goddamn.
一直说这话有什么用 我只是…
What's the point of keep on saying it? All I'm saying.
我没疯 只是陈述事实
I'm not being crazy. I'm stating a fact.
我只说我们不清楚情况
I'm saying we don't know.
直到我们确认这样说
And until we do know, it's not a very nice thing
其实不太好 不是吗  -好吧
-to say, is it? -Okay.
他妈的闭嘴吧
So, fucking stop!
好  -好
Okay. -Okay.
对不起  -没事的
Sorry. -It's okay.
过来 过来
Come here, come here.
我现在要稍微喝一杯 换换心情
Well, I, uh... I'm gonna have a little, uh, stiffener here.
就...先生们
Just... Uh, gents.
卡洛丽娜 失陪
Karolina, pardon me.
让我们为他喝一杯
Let's drink to him.
我想我们都下班了
Well, I guess we're off the clock.
不 我觉得更明智的做法是
No, I think it might be smart for us to..
开始写下时间线
start putting together a timeline
同时 我还在起草联络人名单
And also, I've been drawing up, just in case, you know,
以防万一
if we need to, a contact list
天啊 他才刚刚...他们还在后面
Oh, God! He's just... They're still pumping on him
做心肺复苏呢 卡洛丽娜  -我也
back there, Karolina. -Well, I'm not happy
不想这样 卡尔  -我知道
about it, Karl. -No. No, I know
我知道 我们都心存敬意
And I think we're all being respectful.
我也心存敬意 但这状态
I'm being respectful, but this is going
会变得非常难处理
to be a very complicated situation to handle
所以 如果有奇迹发生
So, you know, if we get a miracle,
上帝保佑我们 我们收获奇迹
we get a miracle. God bless us all.
如果没有 我得做好准备
If we don't, I just have to prepare,
就是这样 对吗  -没错 准备吧
that's all. Right? -Absolutely! Go, go
我们得打给马特森 告诉他这消息
Okay, so I think we should call Mats son and let him know.
然后 我们至少得打给他...
Well, then we should at least call him and tell him that we're..
说他有事耽搁了
that he's delayed.
他可是被大事耽搁了
Oh, he's heavily fucking delayed
然后 没有特定顺序
Yeah. And then, in no particular order
至少跟我说的顺序无关 董事会
not in this order anyway, um, the board.
格丽 总统
Gerri, POTUS, um...
你还好吗
Hey, how are you?
这他妈的 真..
He y, um, that was fucking.
太疯狂了 这太他妈离谱了  -是啊
-nuts! That was fucking crazy, right? -Yeah
是啊  -是的
-Yeah. -It is, it is.
我们...我们都还惊魂未定  -是啊
We were... we're in shock. Yeah. -Yeah
这他妈太诡异了 真要命
That's so fucking weird. Jesus, wow!
你们还好吗  -还行
-You guys okay? -Yeah.
我们还好 谢谢你  -我们还行
-We're good. Thank you. -We're good
凯莉  -怎么了
--Um, Kerry? -Yeah?
你不介意的话 我们要在这里
If it's all right with you, we're just using this space
讨论一个回应
to coordinate a response to, you know
如果我们需要发一个的话...你介意如果..
if we need to send out an... Do you mind if..
可以吗 如果我们...
Is that okay? If we..
没问题... 你想让我来...
But... Yeah. Uh, yeah. Do you... Uh, do you want..
你想让我来帮忙  -不是的
-So, do you want me to help? -Oh, no.
不是这个意思 很感谢你 可你还没缓过来
No, no, that's so kind, but you're in shock
我觉得你应该到后面去
and I think you should go back there.
我们会让你舒服一点
And we'll make you comfortable, and we'll bring you
给你需要的东西 好吗
whatever you need, yeah?
好的 那你想让我...
Okay. So, do you want me to be, uh.
参与其中 还是
part of that, of the response and the...
这样就好 凯莉
That'd be great, Kerry
你先去里面休息吧
Why don't you-rest up in there?
让我们把事情处理妥当 我们会听取你的建议的
Let us get our ducks in a row and we'll get your input
-对  -好的
Yeah. -Okay.
好的  -我这就回来
-Okay. Okay. -Okay, I'm gonna be back here.
过去  -好
-There. -Yes.
这他妈怎么了 -她应该是崩溃了 汤姆
What the fuck? -I think she's freaking out, Tom.
对  -是吗
Yeah. -Oh, yeah?
是的  -看她咧嘴笑
Yeah. -Judging by her grin
还以为她是在洋基体育场捡到了界外球
it looks like she caught a foul ball at Yankee Stadium.
我的天哪  -好了
-I mean, Jesus. -Okay!
这是名单 我觉得 一落地
Here is the list of names. I think we divide up
我们要分工...
as soon as we get the..
不是...不是很清晰 可是
Well, not the... Not the all clear but..
一旦那三十分钟到了...  -其中一些…
once those 30 minutes are up... -Some of those it's.
对你来说太小的事情了 我觉得应该让凯莉来做
It's small for you. I think we should get Kerry to do them
你现在想让凯莉来做吗
Oh, now you want Kerry to do it?
很好  -叫咯咯笑的小丑来吗
Good. -Chuckles the Clown?
算了吧
I think not.
等下
Wait.
稍等一下  -好的
Hold that thought. -Sure
汤姆 你好  -你好 格雷格
-Hey, Tom. -Hey, Greg, hey
我可能需要你帮我去一趟办公室
So, I might need you to whiz into the office for me
今天有婚礼 汤姆 为什么
Um, it's a wedding day, Tom. Why?
为什么 因为洛根死了
Why, um, because Logan is dead
洛根叔公 真的吗 怎么...什么..什么.
Uncle Logan, really? Uh, how... what... what..
所以 听我说 你..你必须紧跟着希德
So, listen to me, you... You have to stick to Cyd
像狗皮膏药那么紧
like a limpet, okay?
然后删掉我标着"后勤"的文件夹
And you delete my folder marked " Logistics,
然后从回收站里也删掉它
And then you delete that from the trash
我还需要你
And I might need you
用我的语气联系大家
calling around with my narrative
唱我的调
You sing my song
圣诞快乐 小格  -什么 什么意思
-Merry Christmas, Greg. -What? What do you mean?
他去世了 你逢凶化吉了
Well, he's passed away and you've lucked out.
你的圣诞袜里藏着什么礼物呢 格雷格
And, yeah, what's at the bottom of your stocking, Greg, huh?
一个讨厌你的老家伙死了
An old guy who fucking hated you
汤姆 拜托
Tom, man!
放松点 老兄..  -抱歉 对不起 抱歉
Easy, dude, like... -I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
你还好吗 天哪
Are you okay? Jesus
我不好 我不好
I'm not okay. I'm not okay
我很悲伤
I'm sad
可是 我很抱歉
Uh, but I'm sorry
对 可是他妈的
Yeah. But, um, Fuck
我不知道 太残酷了
I don't know. It was pretty grim, man
对啊
Yes.
这是个糟糕的...  -我失去了我的保护者
-It's a horrible... -I lost my protector.
好吧 而且...而且..
Okay? And... and
这是绝对机密
... this is total lockdown.
知道吗 格雷格 绝对机密 如果泄露的话
Okay, Greg? Total lockdown. If this leaks,
会是对股价的屠杀
it's a stock price rodeo
大嘴巴的人也要被割喉 明白吗
and a fucking slit throat for the big mouth, okay?
可是 人们...人们应该知道
Okay, but people... people should know
我和他在一起 好吗
that I was with him, okay?
好了 就这样 再见
Okay. Okay, man. Okay, bye
一切还好吗
Everything all right?
是的 没事
Oh, yeah, yeah. Fine, uh.
你叔公能够做到[同义:活下来]吗
Do you think your uncle's gonna make it?
我叔公什么  -抱歉
Do I what? -Sorry.
你叔公能来婚礼吗
Is your uncle gonna make it to the wedding?
你们在这
Hey, guys.
你...什么 你已经知道了 还是
Are you... What? Have you heard already or..
是的 飞机上的同事们认为
Yeah, well, the folks on the plane
我作为联络人在你身边
thought it'd be a good idea for me to act
比较好
as a liaison with you guys
节衰顺变
I am so, so sorry for your loss
我们还什么都不确定 不是吗
Okay, yeah. But we don't know shit, okay?
他们还在救他  -没错 是这样
They're still working on him. -Right, absolutely
万一这是个演习呢 这他妈是个大测验呢
What if this is a drill? What if it's a big fucking test?
你们也不知道  -不知道
-You don't know.  -No.
如果是个测试 我会向企划部门
If it was a test, I'd say hats off
脱帽致敬  -我就是...
-to the planning department. -Yeah, well, I just..
不觉得他已经
It does not feel likely that he's, you know.
你们想让我在外边等候吗
You guys want me to wait outside?
喂 汤姆
Hey, Tom.
好的 谢谢你
Fine. Okay, thank you.
他们停止了心肺复苏
They stopped the CPR
他们不应该停
I don't think they should, though
雨果 卡洛丽娜找你
Yeah. Hugo, Karolina wants you
你好 小卡
Hey, Kay.
都还行
I mean, all good, um.
在..在目前的情况下
under... under the circumstances, yeah
我们要出发了吗  -我们...我们要
-Are we going? -We... we'll.
什么情况
What the fuck?
不不 我...我明白 我们会讨论的
No, no, I... I get it. I'll... I'll.. We'll discuss it.
我们是要离开了  -不行
-Yeah, I think we're going. -No
好的  -我们要去哪
Okay. -Where are we going?
我要挂了 好吗  -雨果 雨果
I gotta go, okay? -Hugo? Hugo?
你能搞明白 这他妈 怎么回事吗
Can you find out what the fuck is going on?
我们要去哪里  -好的 我会的
Where are we going? -Uh, yes, I will
要告诉你们的是 他们…
Uh, and for your information, they're, um,
他们正在起草一份声明
they're starting to draft a statement.
什么意思
How do you mean?
卡洛丽娜和弗兰克 还有..
Uh, Karolina and Frank, and
卡尔和汤姆在整理东西
Karl and Tom are putting something together
等我们准备好发布新闻的时候用
for when we're ready to release the news
他们...他们在拟声明吗
The... they're on the state... statement?
谁让他们这么做的  -我不知道
Who asked them to? -I don't know,
可他们在做了  -这感觉
but they're doing it. -That feels.
这感觉  -对这感觉…
that feels... -Yeah, that feels...
对吧  -是的
-Right? -Yeah.
是  -是
Yeah. -Yeah
雨果 你能快点他妈搞明白
Hey, Hugo, can you fuck off and find out
这条船发生什么了吗
what the fuck's going on with this boat?
好的  -我们想回去
-Yeah. Okay. -We want to go back
好的 我去办 我去办  -快他妈去吧
Yes. I'm on it. I'm on it. -Get the fuck out.
你们好 我打开了免提
Yeah. Hi, folks. Uh, you're on speaker now.
你们好
Hey, uh...
那么 声明是怎么一回事
So, what's going on with this statement?
我们只是 刚开始准备基本框架
Yeah, so we're just starting to put the bones together
等…等我们要宣布的时候用
for when... when we're going to announce this, um.
节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss
这感觉太他妈冒昧了
Oh, okay. Well, feels pretty fucking presumptuous.
抱歉让你们这么想
Uh, well, sorry, that's how it seemed
可是 抛开我们的个人感情
but, you know, regardless of our personal-feeling
就商业角度而言
of loss, in terms of a business position,
这是…这是一个大事件
this is... it is a material event
我们只是需要董事会拿出一些东西
We just need the board to put something together
来安抚市场  -市场吗
to reassure the market. -Oh, the market?
是的 请诸位考虑一下市场
Yes, will someone please think of the market?
我在努力做好本职工作 他现在距离我大概三米
I'm trying to do my job. He's, like, 12 feet away
我认识他四十年了 我们没有硬要做什么
and I knew him for 40 years. We're not pulling anything here.
我们只是觉得 既然你们疏远了
We just thought that since you were estranged
以为你们可能会想让我们来
we thought that you might want us to be
做这件事  -我们没有疏远
-at the hub on this. -We're not estranged
我们没有疏远  -好吧
We weren't estranged. -All right
肯德尔 不是 我的意思只是...
Uh, Kendall, no, I just simply meant that..
我们都和他有过交流
We've all had communications with him.
实际上 我们昨晚还有过家庭聚会
We had a family function last night, in fact
疏远这个词太过了 也不准确
Estranged is a strong word and not accurate.
好的 那就好 我们明白了
Fine. All good. Uh, we got it
那么 我们紧密联系吧
Yeah, look, he y. Uh, let's stay close, huh?
祝你们好运 加油 伙计们
And the best to you guys. Good strength, friends
我想 他们目前
I think, you know, they're very much
还在消化事实
still processing.
这下好了
Fucking great.
该死
Shit
你们怎么样
How are you all doing?
我告诉她了
I briefed her.
真的很遗憾
I'm really sorry
发生了这样的事
I'm very sorry.
他是...
He was...
他对我们每一个人都影响深刻
He was an important man in all our lives
尤其是对你们而言
but especially yours
太感谢你了 格丽 我热泪盈眶了
Thanks, Gerr, I'm welling up.
只是想说 他意味着太多了
I mean, he was a lot of things, but
目前我们还不确定
We don't know yet
他是不是真的去世了 好吗 还没有医生亲眼见过他呢
that he's dead, okay? No doctor has actually seen him
格丽 趁着这会儿间隙
Gerri, in terms of the breathing space,
我们还有时间去思考怎么做的 是吧 在他..
we have a bit of time to think, right? Until he..
你是指  -在他们着陆前
Are you... -Until they land?
你是想在收市之前
Are you thinking, can we hold this information
先把消息给压下来吗
till the markets close?
但是 很显然
Because, obviously
这是影响重大 非常私人的事
this is a very significant, private thing
是吗 有那么重大吗
Is it? Is it significant?
对于公众来说 也是重磅消息
But it's also a big thing in terms of the public
对于公司来说也是  -我现在是真搞不清楚
In terms of the company. -I honestly don't know
还有什么法子了 他们还有多久着陆
how much I can get into this. How long till they land?
我看看 我看看
I will... I will check.
格丽 我们现在思绪有点混乱
Gerri, we can't think straight
可以让他们多在天上呆一会吗
Can we, keep it up there for an extra beat?
能让我们先…  -什么
-Just until we can... you know  -What?
缓一缓  -你是指飞机吗
-while we gather... -The fucking plane?
对 我还没有准备好...
Yeah, I mean, I'm not ready to.
等会 当下之急是把他接到地面来
Wait. We need to get him on the ground
然后找个医生上飞机
We need to get a fucking doctor
给他看看情况  -不 天哪 我头要痛死了
-on that plane. -No. God! I've got a headache.
听着 我觉得你们得冷静下来
Look, I think it's really good
最好先弄清楚情况
for you guys to stay across this.
要不 我去问问他们 能不能让飞机在天上多转几圈
Do you, do you want me to ask if they can circle?
不要  -不要 但...
No. -No, but..
卡洛丽娜  -得在星期一
Karolina. -Not till the markets open
股市开盘之前 只不过是让我们好好想想
on Monday, but just, you know, so we can think?
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
你可以...能麻烦给我
Can you get... Yeah, and can you get me
找些止痛药吗 雨果  -没问题
-an Advil, please? Hugo? -Of course.
我们可以先回陆地上吗
And... and can we get back to fucking land?
我们得先去找他吧  -对
We want to go to him, yeah? -Yeah
谢谢你把格丽带过来 但我们得先回地上
Thanks for getting Gerri, but back to land.
我去办  -麻烦你 感谢
I'm on it. -Do your job, thanks
这一切都太离奇了
Look, this is very surreal
我的意思是
And just to say...
今天我们的所做所言
every single thing we say and do today
都会被记录到回忆录里
is going in the memoirs
会被写到该死的国会记录里
going in the fucking congressional record
会被拿到董事会上讨论 会被记录到
It's coming up at board meetings, it's going
证交所档案里 如果…
in SEC filings. It's like.
要是我们 真的让他们在天上 转半把小时
And we tell them to circle for half an hour
方便我们理清头绪的话 就很有可能
so we can get our heads straight and then some
传出一些该死的言论 他们会说我们冷血无情
fucking rumor starts, we get crucified
成为众天之的 或者还会更严重
for being cold-hearted, or I don't even know.
我们的所作所为 很容易被曲解
We are highly liable to misinterpretation.
所以 我们在老爹去世这天所做的一切
So, what we do today will always be what we did
都将永远被记录下来
the day our father died
所以 我们可以…
So, let... you know, let's..
悲伤哭泣 怎么样都好
grieve and whatever, but..
但 不能做出任何 会影响我们长远之计的事
not do anything that restricts our future freedom of movement
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
要不 我们取消吧 好吗
Let's cancel, yeah?
我觉得已经取消了
I think it is cancelled.
我们怎么和大家说
What do we tell'em?
可能大家都会觉得
I mean, everyone will assume that..
是你主动提出取消的 不过这也无所谓
it's you backing out and that's fine.
或许
Or...
塞翁失马 焉知非福呢 对吧
could something good come out of something bad?
有点奇怪 不是吗
Too weird, right?
对吧  -老康
-Or is it?-Con.
老康 看起来是你想主动取消的
Con, it feels like you kind of want to do it.
我也不清楚 我不..
I don't know. I don't..
有可能..
I guess the truth is..
我怕要是我们不取消的话...
I'm scared if we don't, that.
你就会离开我
that you'll walk away
我一直都害怕你会从我身边走开
I'm always scared you're gonna walk away.
我岁数比你大这么多 威拉
I'm so much older than you, Will a
你这么年轻 这么活泼
You're young and you're full of life,
我又这么...
and I'm...
我也不知道怎么说
I don't know.
我父亲死了 我觉得我也老了
My father's dead and I feel old.
没关系的
It's okay.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
抱歉 我占用了你的青春
I don't know, that I stole you away
你的生命  -老康 别这样
from the world. -Con. Come on, no.
你是为了钱才和我在一起的吗 威拉
Are you just with me for money, Will a?
是吗
Basically?
有部分是为了钱
I mean, there is something about money
和安全感 没错
and safety here, yeah
没错 确实 有这方面因素
Yeah, yeah, there is.
不过
But...
我也确实很开心
I'm happy.
千真万确  -真的吗
-I am. -You okay?
好 好
It's okay.
我不会离开你的
I'm not gonna walk
至少不是今天
Not today anyway
不好意思
I'm sorry.
当时是怎样的情况
What was that like?
他跟你说的时候
When he told you?
我还记得
I thought I knew.
当时 其实我知道可能是爸出事了
And actually, I thought it was Dad
但我却说“是不是妈" 对吧
But I said, " Mom," Right?
没错 你问是不是老妈
Yeah, you asked if it was Mom.
对 我脑子里想的是老爹 但是
Yeah, I was thinking Dad. But I sorta...
我有点
think I...
下意识地 希望是老妈
Think I was hoping it was Mom.
老天  -天哪
-Jesus. -shit.
还有一大堆事情
The fucking lists, the everything.
我不知道还能不能做下去 你没必要硬撑
-I don't know if I can do it. -You don't have to
你不用逼自己去做任何事  我们老爹才刚去世呢
You don't have to do anything, our dad just died.
会好起来的
We'll be okay.
我们找人过来
We'll get people.
给老爹安排一个葬礼
We'll get a funeral off the rack
办个里根那种 加些推文
We can do Reagan's with tweaks
卡洛丽娜在线上
I have Karolina
我和孩子们在一块呢 卡洛丽娜
So, Karolina, I'm with the kids now
我现在要给你开免提了 好吗
and I'm'going to put you on speakerphone, okay?
卡洛丽娜 给你开免提了
Karolina, you're on... You're on speakerphone.
我刚才接到一个记者的电话
Hey, So, I just got a call
也都听说了一些关于洛根身体状况的
from a reporter who's already heard a rumor
谣言
about Logan's... health.
从哪听来的  -我不太清楚信息的来源
-From where? -I don't know what the source was.
我只说没出什么大问题
I just said there was nothing on that
但肯定不是好迹象 但是…
Which is n't great, but..
老天 为什么会这样  -我也不清楚
-Man. How? How? -I don't know.
可能是飞机和地面的通讯被监听了 或者是手机
Plane to ground comms, our tail number
我们在天上盘旋 被他们追踪到了 我也不知道
we're turning, they're tracking. I don't know
目前地面的情况有可能被监听了 又或者是凯莉
what goes on down there. Eavesdrop, Kerry
也许我们只需要
We... We probably do just need
想一想怎么编排一下
to figure out the choreography.
噢 是吗  -目前的流程
-Oh, yeah? -... here.
你想和我死去的父亲编舞一曲
You want to choreograph some steps
是吗 汤姆 跳一段你中意的舞
with my dead father, Tom? That the dance you like?
抱歉
Sorry.
没事 今天对大家来说都很难
That's okay. It's... It's a difficult day
我们需要给公众发布讣告
So, we're gonna need the statement
是你们亲自去发布 还是我们来
Do guys want to do it? Do you want us to do it?
我理解 这对你们很艰难 我理解的
I know that this is tough for you guys, I understand that.
如果你们同意的话 我们可以撰稿
So, if you like, we can give the word
弗兰克 卡尔 我 还有卡罗琳娜 我们可以帮你们
Frank, Karl, myself, Karolina, we could handle
处理当前的杂务 如果你们希望的话
the immediate chowder. And if you like
基于同情原则
you could be excused from
董事会可以不要求你们出席
the board meeting on compassionate grounds
谢谢你 格丽 我要去透透气
Thanks, Gerri. I need some air.
在我们决定之前 能给我们一点时间吗
Can you give us five before we do anything, yeah?
当然了 谢谢
-Yeah, sure. -Thanks!
我不知道
I don't know.
我想说 我..
I mean, I...
我不是很想
I don't really want to be
做那个出头的人 我感觉
the one to have to say things. I feel like
你们都在等着我说话 我懂 但是
you're looking at me and, yeah, but.
没关系的
It's okay.
肯
Ken.
没关系 我们…
It's okay. We..
你可以说 “我没有什么想法”
You can say, " I don't think anything of it.
这也没问题的  -好吧 我是觉得
It's... You can say. -Okay. I mean, just.
谁知道呢 也许明天
I mean, who knows? Maybe we.
我们交出王冠
Tomorrow, hand in the crown
或许也是个不错的主意 把交易结束 功德圆满
probably a good idea, finish the sale, great
不过
but just...
我们是不是该保留选择的机会呢
Should we keep our options open?
雨果 再等一下
One second, Hugo
是啊 我只是觉得 现在这个时候
Um, yeah, I just don't know that I can
我真的做不了任何事 跟任何人说话
literally do anything or talk to anyone
但是 我们得去发表声明 罗曼
We need to be on the statement though, Rome
我知道  -不然的话
-I know. --Otherwise.
这些事情就全部落到弗兰克 卡尔 还有格丽 他们手里去了
it could be all Frank and Karl and... and Gerri and..
那样的话 不管声明的内容如何 经过一夜與论发酵之后
You know, even just overnight, whatever the text is
潜台词都会变成
the subtext has to be..
洛根·罗伊结束了 但是罗曼·罗伊还有肯道尔·罗伊
Logan Roy, you know. But Roman Roy and Kendall Roy
还有小西·罗伊我们要站在一起 好吗
and Shiv Roy. We're all here, yeah?
好吧
Okay, and..
我只是不愿意交给卡罗利娜去处理这些事
I just don't want Karolina to just handle it..
只是这个声明而已  -好吧
It's just for this statement. -Okay
你知道的 后面的事董事会来决定
You know, it'll be for the board to decide
但是 我觉得在那之前
But... but I think until then.
为了股市考虑
you know, just for the markets.
我们需要掌控局面
we need to be in control
我们一起  -是的
Us. -Yeah
直到董事会开始
Until the board can meet
好吧 我会的
Yeah, uh-huh, I mean, I would
我不希望 出现任何 没经过我们许可的 自作主张的
I don't want anything happening that we don't, like, approve, so
就这样
Yeah.
好吗
Yeah
雨果
Hugo?
我们会拟好声明
We'll draft the statement, okay?
很好 很好
Great. Great. Great
我们需要他们的署名
Um, we'll need them to sign off
弗兰克也好 西蒙也好 或者董事会联名
It'll need to come from Frank, or Simon, or the board..
对 但是由我们来起草 好吧
Yeah, but we'll draft, okay?
那谁去给马特森打电话
And who will call Mats son?
我知道 但是
I know but..
抱歉 我得挂电话了
Oh, I gotta get off the phone, sorry
靠  -好啦 好啦
-Fuck me. -Okay. Okay
你好  -你好
I Hey. -Hey.
那个 我需要在这个房间单独呆会
Uh, yeah. I kind of need the room
当然 没问题
Oh, sure, of course.
我...
I'm, uh.
我很难过
I'm pretty sad.
应该说 其实我现在完全是麻木的
I mean, I'm actually, right now, totally numb
不过理论上 你会觉得我很...
but theoretically, you would say that I'm..
对 我就是很难过  -是啊
-Yeah, that I'm sad. -Yeah.
好了 这个房间都是你的了
Well. The room's all yours
我脑子里乱糟糟的
It's a fucking mess.
好吧
Okay.
来了  -我不知道该说什么
-Hey. -I don't know what to say.
我很抱歉
Sorry. I'm so sorry, I.
嘿 真让人难过
-Hey. -I'm so sorry.
是啊
Yeah
那个 我们要怎么把他带下来
Hey. Uh, how are we getting him off?
我也不知道 天哪 我会处理好的
Uh, I don't know, Jesus. U h, I'll handle it
你们准备好了声明材料了吗
You... you got the edits on the statement?
我们觉得要稳住市场 我们得提一下卡尔
We do feel that for market competence, it's important for Karl
我还有格丽的名字
myself and Gerri to be mentioned by name
好的 我马上去办
Great, I'll get that out right away
看啊
Uh, and, look, we got
这里到处都是想拍照放料的人
shutterbugs all over the perimeter
要是我们不发言的话
and we're looking at a feeding frenzy
舆论就要炸了 我们得让他们自家人
if we don't talk. So, we're gonna
出来发言
get some comments from the family
我已经准备好为我们说话的人  -做好自己的工作
-and I primed our friendlies. -Duty calls
新闻发布会那里举行
O h, uh, the press conference is happening in there
孩子们已经到了
and the kids are already in, so..
我就先…   -好 快去吧
I'm gonna... -Yeah. Go, go, go. Yeah, I know.
你好...
Hey. Hi. So.
大家好
Hello. Hello, everyone.
我们会没事吧
Are we gonna be okay?
当然
Yeah. Yeah.
我们能搞定的
We'll be okay
你不会没事的
You're not gonna be okay
你也一样 不会好的
Well, you're not gonna be okay either
你不会好的
You're not gonna be okay
你完蛋了 你完蛋了
-You're fucked. -You are fucked
你彻底完蛋了 -你不能更完蛋了
You're totally fucked. -You're very fucked
好了 大家都准备好了吗  -好了
-Okay. Hi. Everybody ready? -Yeah
小西  -准备好了吗
-Shiv? -Ready?
确定吗
Sure?
好的
All right.
我...谢谢大家
I... Thank you.
如各位所知 我的父亲洛根·罗伊 于今天下午
As you know, my father, Logan Roy, was pronounced dead
在到达泰特波罗机场后 被宣告死亡
on arrival at Teterboro Airport this afternoon
感谢媒体们在此刻对于逝者的尊重
I'd like to thank the press for their respect at this time.
希望你们理解 我不会接受任何采访
You'll understand that I won't be taking any questions
我和我的兄长们只想说
But my brothers and I just want to say
洛根·罗伊建立了一个伟大的美国家族企业
that Logan Roy built a great American family company
正如各位了解到的情况 本司领导权的去向
And as you know, the board will be convening
将在不久后
in the next hours to decide on the leadership
由董事会开会决定
of the company going forward
民族失去了一个热情的捍卫者
This nation has lost a passionate champion
国家失去了一个巨人 我们失去了深爱的父亲
and an American Titan, and we lost a beloved father
感谢各位的聆听  -那么请问
-Thank you. -And in terms
你们将在公司担任什么样的角色呢
of your roles at the company?
我们希望
We intend to..
我们希望带领公司走过
We intend to shepherd it through it's
不管未来怎样 我们都会守在这
Whatever its future may be, but we'll be there.
这是我们共同的意愿
We intend to be there
谢谢大家 不要提问了
Guys, guys, thank you! No more questions!
各位 请不要再提问了
Guys, no more questions. No more questions, please
给这个家庭留一些隐私吧
Respect the privacy of the family
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
来了
Hey.
他来了
There he is.
这就是老爸
That is Dad.
好了 那我们要去看他吗
Okay, so, we gonna go see him?
你想去吗
Do you want to?
难道不应该去吗
Shouldn't we?
毕竟我们不去 他也不会生气了
I mean, he's not gonna get angry if we don't.
是啊 好吧
Yeah, right.
汤姆 你能不能…
Hey, Tom! Can you..
再说一遍当时的情况
go through it again? What happened?
我要去...去看看他
I'm gonna go... I'm gonna go see him
你想过去吗
Do you wanna?
我 我的话...
Uh, I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
就在这里看他下来  -好
watch him down from here. -Okay
好的...
Okay, so...
行吧 就这样
Yeah. Okay.